Yes, so the meeting is over.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Hori.
I'm curious about you, too, Yabana.
Aren't you curious about what's popular among young people these days?
Well, yes.
I think things have probably already changed a lot.
I'm very curious.
Junior high school students have computers that have been handed out at school since the first grade,
Seriously? Nobody sharpened their pencils.
Oh, man.
Seriously?
So they play games on the computer during lunch break.
Oh, yeah.
A computer.
The school gives you one?
It's a loaner computer.
Do some students take it home with them?
Yes, we take it home with us. All of us.
Wow...
It's kind of nice.
Yeah, it's nice.
Damn.
Wow, that's great.
Do you use the computer for class notes?
Notes. Sometimes I write my opinions on the computer.
Wow.
That's like college.
That's what I do.
It's true.
That's amazing.
Wait, wait, wait.
You know, on the campus notebook, you know, the campus part,
You don't put a makie around every single part of the campus?
I don't think I do that sometimes.I don't think I do that on campus sometimes.
Ehhhhh.
I have.
Oh, yes, I have.
You do deco it. The letters that say "campus" on it.
Like this.
Then you trace over it one more time with a magic marker.
It's amazing. I don't get it.
I don't get it.
That's right.
But do you use notebooks now?
Yes, I do.
But I mostly write my opinions on a computer or something.
Do you have a notebook?
Yes, I have a notebook.
I have a number pad.
What is the account that you submit? A notebook.
I only submit Japanese.
Other than that, I don't do it at all.
No, but there were quite a few.
Since that time, I've been wondering if it would be better to keep the number sheets as they are,
Or should I write down my own opinion?
Is that what you are doing now?
In my Japanese notebooks, I write the numbers on the top,
I have to write my opinion at the bottom.
That's amazing. I wish I could have done it that way.
I wish I could have done it that way.
Are there any ballpoint pens allowed?
No.
That's true.
Everyone is doing their best with mechanical pencils.
I knew it.
Are there people who sometimes kick loudly?
Yes, there are.
I wonder. There are people who are really loud.
During tests, they are very noisy.It's very noisy during tests.
What do you mean "noisy"?
But I was doing it a little bit.
I'm noisy.
It's just something that happens on its own.
I understand.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
I apologize to everyone in the classroom.
That's right. It's not like that anymore.
It's already different.
High school is different, right?
I'll buy a tablet for high school. At the time of entrance.
What about textbooks?
I have textbooks, but I buy a tablet and put the textbooks in the tablet...
I buy a tablet and put all the textbooks in the tablet, and I do it on the tablet, and I don't even have to do the bookkeeping, it's all sprints.
I don't even have to write a book, it's all sprints these days.
And all the submissions are on the tablet, like reports.
Yeah. 〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜
Your bag looks light.
It is light.
I wish I had a bag like that when we were kids,
I had a bag, and this string was so stretched out.
I love it.
I can do everything on my tablet.
I'm so jealous.
I bet you watch YouTube during class.
I don't watch it.
You're a fighter.
That's true.
But I usually play tag or something. I haven't changed since elementary school.
You do that.
but I kind of hate going outside.But I'm kind of sick of being out there.
We're all drawing on the blackboard
It's so nice, isn't it?
You can't play tag on a computer.
It's a little difficult.
What about high school?
In high school, we all talk together.
But everyone gets so sleepy in class.
After high school, during break time, everyone just lies down on their desks.
Sleeping.
I don't have the energy to run around in junior high anymore.
It's gone.
They're either sleeping like this or they're playing games on their tablets.
Or they're playing games on their tablets.
Oh, wow.
Sounds fun. I see.
In high school, during recess, everyone was fixing their pencils.
But everyone goes to the bathroom before Kagami.
They do their bangs, too.
It's totally different.
I think there are people who try to accept the school rules, like taking pictures for social networking and TikTok.
Do you do any of those things? In high school...
Do you film each other with your friends?
I don't really do that, but when I was in elementary school, TikTok was really popular.
In elementary school?
That's right.
Yuck!
So we were filming at home.
Oh, yeah.
What did you do?
We used to dance together.
In elementary school.
Cute. You were already an idol then.
Really?
Really?Yeah. - Yeah!
Yeah!
We can film on TikTok or something.
We are not allowed to use TikTok inside the school building.
So after school, for example, there are a lot of students who take pictures when they go out with their friends.
What?
You don't take Purikura?
Yes, we take Purikura!
I'll take Purikura.
You don't want to take Purikura? I'll go with you.
I'll go take Purikura after school.
Purikura nowadays don't have graffiti, right?
Not really.
I don't.
I don't do it much.
Oh...
Did you ever see a stamp that said "our friendship is eternal"?
No.
No?
Wait, I looked.
Oh, yeah, there was.
It's like a two-for-one.
I don't see it.
I'm not writing anything down.
Nothing?
Yes, sir.
Then what are you doing during that doodle time?
I choose to do some kind of makeup.
Oh, I see. I see.
It's not doodling anymore.
Make your face pretty and slanted.
That's right.
That's better.
You're right.
We don't have time for stamping.This is no time for stamping.
Oh, really?
What's that?
You're not from my generation?
You seem a little shocked.
Let's just go.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's funny.
How'd it go? Well, you know.
I'm a little shocked at how far away from school I am.
I mean, I've been out of high school for almost six years now.
That's a long time.
That's amazing.
But I'm sure the kids now have new ways to have fun.
I kind of want to be a student again.
Wear the uniform.
I want to wear a uniform one more time.
I want to take the tablet!
Every summer that notebook is a little wrinkled from sweaty hands
Sweaty hands.
Really?
How can you tell?
You can tell.
I see.
It's getting a little sad.
Well, now that the mood has turned a little somber...
I'd like to end with the conclusion of this venue.
Well, I was a little shocked.
Thank you very much.